A gentleman over there – you have two wives.
You don’t know how you came about these two wives; they live separately.
You will not be able to continue this life – it is too tough, too difficult for you.
You scraped your hair.
He is a young man with a t-shirt with some pictures on it.
Yes.
You will not be able to cope; you just need God’s intervention to save you.
You will not be able to cope this time because people may see you as very hilarious;
he is a gentleman; it is just appearance.
My name is Gabriel.
I come from the Republic of Benin.
Don't mind my English because I'm not from Nigeria.
This is my lovely wife.
This is my first daughter.
This is my lovely second daughter.
I came here last week for the first time and the man of God prophesied that someone had two wives
and they were not in the same country; they were in different countries.
When the man of God said this, my conscience told me that I wasn’t here for this so don’t rise up.
Then, I kept sitting.
But when he repeated it the second time, I don’t know what pushed me to the front.
Then I said, “Yes, Man of God, the prophecy is mine”.
I am a marine man; I used to work in Lagos.
I supply vessels.
For over three years, my business is not moving.
I used to travel to Ghana and Lome, Togo for my work.
Anywhere I went, women used to love me.
Even if I met them for the first time, they used to fall in love with me.
My business was not moving at all.
I went to many places for solution but there was no way.
One of my friends introduced me to The SCOAN last week, I came and the man of God prophesied to me.
With the work I used to do in Nigeria, I used to stay four to five months before going back to Benin.
So, my family and my wife used to miss me because when I came to Lagos,
I used to have many women so, I wouldn’t bother about my family.
She would be calling me and I would tell her not to worry, that I had come to make money and
when I had money, I would come home.
I could stay for five months but no money.
I would go back home and she would feed me.
I tried my best; I went to Ghana.
If the white men came, they would call me at Ghana or Lome.
If I went there, I would do the work, the money would come but I wouldn't know how the money went.
I didn’t usually come home with anything.
When I came for my first time, last week, the man of God prophesied to me.
I said, "Yes, truly; but this was too much".
I thought to myself that I should get another wife.
I went out in Lagos, found another lady and got married to her, which my wife doesn’t know about.
What the man of God said is true.
I didn’t expect that in my life this secret could leak out because my wife is in Benin,
while the other woman is staying in Lagos.
I brought my wife here once but when I got the second wife, I didn’t bring her anymore.
You mean that today is the first time your wife is hearing of this?
It is the first time that my wife is hearing this.
Even the lady that I am talking about now, the man of God said I should invite her and she is here now.
My wife does not know her.
Please, I want the man of God to help me settle my family.
This has destroyed my business.
When I came here, what the man of God said means that through this, my business is not moving.
My wife and children are not happy with me.
That is why my business has a breakage.
Please, Man of God, help me and reconcile my family for me.
My name is Florence.
I am from Benin.
It is because of the prophecy that I got to know that my husband is having a woman outside.
When he used to tell me that he is going to work, I never thought that he was doing a different thing.
When he leaves the house, he can stay outside for three months
and when he comes back, he is never really happy.
Just for a little thing, he can get annoyed and begin to shout at me.
So, I am asking the man of God to save my marriage because presently, I am living in
my parents' house because of the financial problem we have.
I stay at the house of my parents.
So, I am asking the man of God to save me and to save my marriage.
After accommodating Mr Gabriel & his family in The SCOAN, the following Sunday,
Prophet T.B. Joshua counsels the family and also Mr Gabriel’s second wife,
telling them the mind of God about their future and praying for them in Jesus' name.
I also got married to this lady in Lagos.
You got married?
How many months now?
In August, it will be two years.
Give me your hand.
And my sister hearing it...
For her to even follow you here, she just wants to channel her own course and her own direction;
she is not interested and sees it as a past tense event.
Mistakes are correctable.
When we learn from our mistakes, we move on.
I want to say to my sister, I am your brother; I am at your service.
We shall meet after the prayer.
We can ask God the direction.
OK?
This is a family already that God has brought together.
It is just satan who came to try and separate this family; we thank God it is over today.
Thank you very much.
OK?
Since you have not talked of having a child between you and her, nothing like that?
No.
OK
Glory be to God.
Thank you very much.
It is not an issue you should raise at home; rather, put it behind you.
If you raise this issue anytime there is trouble, you begin to make jest of your husband
or remind him of his past, you also may be tempted because the Bible says
when one is caught out of sin or wrong, you who caught such a person should restore them gently
so that you will not be tempted.
OK?
Thank you.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Counsels Mr Gabriel & His Wife After The Sunday Service
Thank you, Man of God, I understand.
Thank you very much.
The right knowledge of God settles peace.
After the counselling, Prophet T.B. Joshua prays for Mr Gabriel and his family in the power of the Holy Spirit.
TESTIMONY TIME
My name is Gabriel.
I am from the Republic of Benin.
I am 38 years old.
The lady beside me is my lovely wife.
Her name is Florence.
You are both welcome, sir.
Can you just tell us what God Almighty has done for you since coming to The SCOAN?
Two weeks ago, I came to the service and the man of God prophesied that
there was somebody who had two wives who were not staying in the same country,
which was my prophesy.
Then, I rose up very surprised because he said the story of my life and I said, I was the one.
The man of God invited me to come with those two women to settle our lives.
Then, I brought them here.
That was when the man of God told me that because I had been cheating on my wife,
that things had turned upside down for me because I was not straight forward with her.
When I was working, all my things were upside down, my business collapsed, nothing went on.
I believe that any time from today when I apologise to God and her
that things will get better in the name of Jesus.
What he advised me to do was to stop looking outside and face my wife and family.
Then, my life will change.
I believe that and I apologise to my wife, that the past should be the past,
let us take steps towards what we are about to start genuinely.
So, I thank God.
Glory be to God.
Prophet T.B. Joshua counselled you that after the prophecy you should stay faithful to your wife
and that you should disconnect from the relationship with the other lady outside.
You are saying that right now you are actually asking for forgiveness from your wife
and you are promising that you are not gonna betray her again, that you gonna be faithful and stay with her.
Yes, truly – backwards never.
I am straight forward now with my wife and I promise her that all this is in the past.
The past cannot come to the present again.
I promise her one hundred percent of my new life.
My heart used to be heavy but now, I am light.
There are a lot of changes in my life and I thank God for all this.
We thank God for our brother's life and for the reconciliation that has taken place in his marriage
through that prophetic word and the counsel from Prophet T.B. Joshua.
There are a lot of changes in my life and I thank God for all this.
Thank You, Jesus.
My name is Florence.
I am from Benin.
Who is the man beside you?
It is my husband.
When I came to the church, I heard the prophecy given to my husband and I thank God for it.
I forgive him for all he has done and I ask God to give us a long life together.
I want to advise other women to take heart; no matter what happens in your home, have faith.
There is a God who is above all and takes care of all; just be patient and courageous.
Prophecy Testimony
We thank God for this wonderful word of advice and we salute our sister here
for really choosing to stay in the marriage despite everything that happened.
Hallelujah. We thank God once again.
We are here right now with a message from Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Prophet T.B. Joshua said that now, as you have started this new chapter in your marriage, a new life in Christ
after this reconciliation, that he wants to support this family.
On behalf of Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV partners,
we are presenting you with this gift of 100, 000 naira.
This is to encourage this family to stay close to Jesus Christ and make the word of God
the standard for their lives and use this to start a fresh chapter in their lives,
now that the reconciliation has come, in the name of Jesus Christ.
Amen.
I thank Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV partners for all they have done.
May God be with them and bless them more.
Thank You, Jesus!
Mr. Gabriel And His Wife Receive 100,000 Naira From Prophet T.B. Joshua & Emmanuel TV Partners